Hello.
こんにちは
This is Songtan.
ソンタンです
ソ ンタンです
That's it, Sontan.
イ ッチだ、ソンタン
Please ask me a question.
質問をね
ask a question
質問を
hey.
ね
Are you on your knees?
膝 の地になってますか?
S-cup.
エスカップ
Once again, aren't you surprised?
ちょっともう一回、 びっくりしたんじゃない?
One more time, one more time.
どんどん一回、もう一回
I'm surprised.
びっくりだよ
Because everyone around the world is waiting for presents.
世界中の プレゼント待ってる みんなが 気になってるから
There's a present packed inside, right?
ちょっとこの中にさ、 プ レゼント詰まってるでしょ?
It's packed with presents.
プレゼント詰まってる
It's cute.
可愛いね
Is it okay to cry?
泣いていい?
Open it.
開けて
I'm fine.
元気よ
Take it out.
出して
I can't see it.
見えない
I've never been a good girl.
いい子もしてたことない
It makes me laugh so much
めっちゃ笑うじゃ
yeah.
ん
Not the face.
顔 じゃない
Don't stay in your shell all the time.
ずーっと殻ないで
As expected, it's not too itch.
さすがにイッチすぎない
I felt embarrassed.
恥ずかしくなった
TRUE?
本当?
happy.
嬉しい
I was a good girl.
いい子にしてたもん
You promised.
約束してたもんね
How much is the present?
プレゼント何くらい?
thing.
もの
anything.
なんでも
I want the whole thing.
まるごと欲しい
I want to fuck my body too.
体もむちゃくちゃにしたいよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
What can I do?
何してもいいの?
It's okay if you don't say anything.
何も言わないってことは いいってことだよ
I can't help but love you.
好きにしていて たまんないんだけど
It gets really intense and we end up having sex.
濃くいっちゃいっちゃセックスしちゃう
I'm starting to like it more and more.
どんどん好きになってくるし
You haven't let me have sex with you lately.
最近ずっと イッチさしてくれなかったもんね
I told you to save it.
溜めとけって言ったから
Yeah.
うん
Is that so?
そうなの?
Is it pan-pan?
パンパンやんか
I can't even put it in anymore.
もう入れてもないの
I'm going to hit my hip.
腰打っちゃう
Great underwear underneath too.
下もすっごい下着
Take a look.
ちょっと見してよ
Very Christmas colors.
めっちゃクリスマスカラーを
It's already a little too crazy.
ちょっともうヘロすぎるって
Please leave it and watch it.
残し見てね
I can almost see this.
これほぼ見えちゃってる
Can you give me this as a present?
これをプレゼントしてくれる?
I can see it.
見えちゃったね
It's so beautiful.
すーごい綺麗だね
You saw that.
あれ見えたね
This is too sexy.
セクシーすぎるってこれ
This one is also coming out a little bit.
こっちもちょっと出ちゃってる
He's a really naughty guy.
すーごいイッチな地首してる
Can I know?
知っていい?
Can I lick your sweetness now?
もうその甘おこさを舐めていい?
It's not moving.
動いてない
I fell really hard.
すっごい落ちちゃった
Down here, my nose fell out a little.
この下さ、 鼻ちょっと抜けた
That's about it.
これそのくらいで
I think I'm about to go.
ちょっと、もういっちゃいそう
I've already put out a lot.
もういっぱい出しちゃった
I was so nervous that I ended up using my mouth.
緊張すぎてお口でいっちゃった
What happened?
どうなんでした?
I can't push it up.
押し上げないもんね
I can't take it away.
取り切れない
It's totally possible
全然ありゃあり
Yeah.
ゃ
I'm wearing it.
着 てるよ
It's gone.
無くなっちゃったね
There isn't one.
無いじゃん
Do you like the style?
スタイルいい?
I'm wearing chin chin again.
またチンチン着てきちゃった
Is it okay to put penis in?
チンチン入れすっていいかな?
This is over.
これきっちゃった
Probably not.
たぶんないわ
I like your great style.
すごいスタイルいいね
I wore it really well.
すごい着ちゃった
I just fell.
今落ちちゃった
What kind of character was it?
どんな字だったんだっけ?
ど んな字だったんだっけ?
Gil.
ギル
Thunder Thunder.
サンダーサンダー
It's a bunny.
バニーじゃん
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いじゃん
You're inviting me.
誘ってるよね
There's nothing else.
それ以外無いよね
Isn't it cold?
寒くないの?
I'm hiding here though.
ここ隠れてるけどさ
He says it's surprisingly warm.
意外と温かいって言う
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
It's cold now, isn't it?
今は寒いでしょ
I can't say anything because I'm so hungry.
お腹がひとんだこと言えない
The two of us need to warm up more and more.
どんどん二人で温まらないといけない
I'm going to pitch.
投手しちゃう
My body temperature was surprisingly warm.
意外と体温あったかいんだけど
Thunder Thunder.
サ ンダーサンダー
Tsuru.
つ る
Vine.
つる
Amazing slime opper.
すごいスライムオッパー
It's the first time I've ever looked this cute.
こんな可愛そうになって初めて
You can almost see it.
ほぼ見えちゃってるよね
Let's even try it.
すらしてみよう
A cute chikuri came out.
かわいいちくり出てきた
It's not that embarrassing, is it?
そんな恥ずかしくないでしょ
What is this?
これとは?
Isn't there something strange?
変 わんなくない?
It's so warm.
すっごい温かい
It's the original.
元だぜ
amazing.
すごい
Is this underwear?
これ下着と?
The role below.
下の役割が
Anno?
あんの?
this.
これ
It's digging into my underwear.
下着食い込んでる
It sounds a little naughty.
ちょっとエッチな音するね
This is over my underwear, after all.
一応これ下着越しだから
It doesn't make any sense.
意味ないね
I'll shift it.
ずらしちゃう
It's really humid.
お湿気すごいもんね
It's so wet.
すっごい濡れてる
I don't think I can get any hot water into this.
全然これ湯も入りそう
Melting.
トロトロ
Super naughty Thunder Thunder.
すごいエッチのサンダーサンダー
If only I could understand.
もう一応分かられたら
I'm starting to get scared.
怖がってきちゃった
It doesn't have any meaning as underwear.
下着としての意味出してない
I want you to do something about it.
どうにかしてほしい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Try using candy for a while.
ちょっと飴使いじゃなめてみて
Use your hands.
手を使ってさ
It's intense.
激しくさ
Don't be violent.
激しくしない
I might go.
行きそうかも
A little Christmas present.
ちょっとクリスマスプレゼント
Is it Christmas?
クリスマスか
Jinkle veil.
ジンクルベール
Thank you Sander.
ありがとうサンダーさん
This gift was given to me by me.
このプレゼント、俺からあげちゃった
Our people.
僕らの人
I got it.
もらった
It's a Jinkle veil.
ジンクルベールだよね
I want you to smoke just a little bit of what's left of your present.
プレゼント残りちょっとだけ吸ってほしい
My hands are empty again.
また手が空きちゃった
I might still be able to go.
まだいけるかも
Can I have a bite?
一口入れていいかな?
I just gave it as a present.
プレゼントしたばっか
I'm very energetic.
め っちゃ元気ある
Look here.
こっち見て
Can I write this?
これが書いていい?
It's written in half-width.
半角着書だ
Can you lie down?
薄伏せになれる?
Lay down.
薄伏せ
Can I cum inside you?
中 出していい?
Will you give me another present?
またプレゼントくれるの?
I'm here.
いらっしゃるよ
It's a white Christmas.
ホワイトクリスマスだな
White Christmas.
ホ ワイトクリスマス
Vanilla Thunder?
バニラサンダー?
What sounds too sexy?
何の音がセクシーすぎるね
I thought this was just one side, but it's actually a bra.
これ片表かと思ったらブラだね
Sugo
すーご
stomach.
い
Let's overlap.
重 ねるね
I can't really see the point.
しっかりめっちゃ便観が見えない
I'm feeling nervous here.
ここにコリコリしてる
This is erotic.
エロいなこれ
This is the thread that you can see for yourself.
自分で見える糸これ
First, try spreading your legs.
一番で足を広げてみて
Do you hit a place that feels good?
気持ちいいところ当たる?
Where should I take it out when I go?
いくときどこ出せばいいの?
Can I cum inside you?
中出していいの?